







Asadollah Heidari

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

intern, Front End Team Saafaa company.



Saffaa Knowledge-Based Company actively produces open-source software based on spatial information and GIS.

March 2021 to August 2021 (6 months)

- I got acquainted with the principles of web and front programming
- www.saafaa.ir

Front End Developer Sahim Company.

June 2022 to November 2024 (**2 year and 5 months**) - <u>www.sahimco.ir</u>



- Development of an intelligent transportation system for Yazd municipality www.otoman.yazd.ir
- Development of the citizen service system <u>www.my.yazd.ir</u>
- Development of citizenship payment system
- Development of SSO system
- Development of AVL system

What I did on the team:

- 1) Development of components using MUI
- 2) Participation in the analysis of software features
- 3) R&D on the use of technologies
- 4) Writing tests for JavaScript components and functions
- 5) Using different libraries such as Redux Toolkit, React Query, Axios,...
- 6) Creating a technical document for the project And More

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelor of software engineer

Yazd University | 2018 - 2022

LinkedIn Profile

<u>linkedin.com/in/asad-heidari-9197831b7/</u>

asadheidariir@gmail.com +98 921 357 8643

Yazd, Iran

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript

ReactJs, NextJs

MUI, Chakra, Ant Design, Tailwind CSS

SASS, Redux, React Query,

Git, Github, Gitlab, Docker

Figma

Map: Leaflet, Maplibre



ABOUT ME

I am a passionate software engineer and developer who has always loved creating new and innovative projects. My journey in software development allows me to experience the joy of building exciting solutions. I am committed to continuous learning and embracing new challenges. Working in a collaborative team environment is highly fulfilling, and I look forward to contributing to your team and building exceptional products together.